The whole world
sees your life's
work go up
in flames, and
you say that
salvation and
healing are
near to
come. Yes.
How? Yes. Truly,
it wasn't... truly,
we understood that
we were in
an event far
bigger than us,
by hundreds
of times.
This wasn't our
event. We felt
it in that
very moment, that
God does here
what He wants.
We simply leaned
back and said:
we are in
Your hands,
Master of
the world.
That was the
reality. When I
got here and
realized that there
was only damage
to property, something
in me burst
into a psalm
of thanksgiving. We
said: "Mizmor L'Toda,
shout for
joy to
the Lord."
Thank God that
our loss was
only of objects
- of wood
and stone.
And then
this weekend,
with Benayahu...
I truly
felt a
kind of
gratitude this
week.
And I
wasn't so
devastated, but
now this
murder of
Benayahu -
that was
the straw
that broke...
that's what
made this
event so
much harder.
Practically speaking, what
is the immediate
thing you need
right now?
Our understanding is
that the immediate
thing that can
really help us,
right here and
now, is partnering
with us in
the Tzameret campaign
- saving
Tzameret at
Chavat Gilad.
We understand that
we need to
take responsibility, also
for the sake
of Chavat Gilad,
because there will
be nothing to
deal with
such a
huge event.